

CONTACT

- **** 0728726668
- youngbk0308@gmail.com
- 63 Olive Road, EASTRIDGE, Mitchell's Plain, 7785
- https://bit.ly/3SXCMej



https://byron-young-portfoliov2.vercel.app/

EDUCATION

Jan 2021 - Dec 2023

Cape Peninsula University of **Technology**

DPICTADIP: ICT in Applications Development

Jan 2008 - Dec 2012

Princeton High School

National Senior Certificate

TECH STACKS



LANGUAGES

• English (Fluent)

BYRON YOUNG

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Junior developer with two years' experience in a software development environment. I have completed my diploma in Information & Communication Technology at Cape Peninsula University of Technology. I am an excellent communicator, problem solver, and team player. My career objective is to become a Full Stack Developer, as I am constantly seeking opportunities to learn new technologies to improve my skills. I am excited to bring my skills and passion to a new role in the field of software development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Cape Peninsula University of Technology JULY 2023 - DEC 2023 Intern Developer
 - · Upskill myself by watching online courses.
 - Develop a Virtual Machine request application.

University of Western Cape

MAY 2018 - MAY 2019

Intern Developer

- · Collaborated with a senior developer in developing an application using SSIS.
- Editing project documentation.
- Collaborating with team members on GitHub.

Web 2 Web

MAY 2017 - NOV 2017

Intern Web Developer

- · Create a webpage for a client.
- · Add content to client's website.
- Help grow client's online presence by using SEO practices

REFERENCE

Ageel Bucks

University of Western Cape

Position: Senior Developer

Phone: 0613548781

Malibongwe Dywibiba

Cape Peninsula University of Technology

Position: ICT Department Supervisor

Phone: 083 494 2638